Writings by Lowell Thomas
Marist Archives and Special Collections
Writings by Lowell Thomas
1.25.2.6
Marist College
  Box 505
- Writings by Lowell Thomas, 1.25.2.6
  - The Land of the Kangaroo, Boomerang and Bushranger, 1920 December 1; 1 (Box 505)
  - Journal notes (India), 1922; 2 (Box 505)
  - A City of a Thousand and One Sins, circa 1922; 3 (Box 505)
  - Too Many Bowls of Bhang, circa 1922; 4 (Box 505)
  - Freebooters of the Afghan Border, circa 1922; 5 (Box 505)
  - Dale Carnegie: An Appreciation [also known as Dale Carnagey], circa 1930s; 6 (Box 505)
  - Lowell Thomas Remembers the Allenby and Lawrence Show (transcript), undated; 7 (Box 505)
  - Lowell Thomas Remembers Palestine (transcript), undated; 8 (Box 505)
  - Lowell Thomas Remembers India (transcript), undated; 9 (Box 505)